Thank you very much. Now, I've got a story for you.
Muchas gracias. Tengo una historia que contaros.
When I arrived off the plane,
Cuando bajé del avión,
after a very long journey from the West of England,
después de un largo viaje desde el oeste de Inglaterra,
my computer, my beloved laptop,
mi ordenador, mi querido portátil,
had gone mad,
se había vuelto loco
and had -- oh! -- a bit like that! --
y había...¡Ah!...¡Algo así!
and the display on it --
y la pantalla...
anyway, the whole thing had burst.
...bueno, se rompió todo.
And I went to the IT guys here
Fuí a ver a los chicos de Tecnologías de la Información
and a gentleman mended my computer,
y un caballero arregló mi ordenador
and then he said, "What are you doing here?"
y me preguntó: "¿Qué te ha traído aquí?"
and I said "I'm playing the cello and I'm doing a bit of singing,"
y le dije: "Vengo a tocar el chelo y a cantar un poco"
and he said, "Oh, I sort of play the cello as well."
él dijo: "Yo también toco el chelo"
And I said, "Do you really?"
Y yo le dije: "¿En serio?"
Anyway, so you're in for a treat,
Y aquí está, para pasar un buen rato
because he's fantastic, and his name's Mark.
porque ¡es fantástico! Se llama Mark.
(Applause)
(Aplausos)
I am also joined by my partner in crime, Thomas Dolby.
Me acompaña también mi cómplice, Thomas Dolby.
This song is called "Farther than the Sun."
Esta canción se llama "Más lejos que el sol".
(Music)
(Música)